Guide to the Stanford Report
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford Report
1957-2015
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University. University Relations
Stanford University. News and Publications Service
Stanford University. Office of Public Affairs
2000/4
58 volume(s)
Universities and colleges -- Periodicals; Stanford University. University Relations; Stanford University. News and Publications Service; Stanford University. Office of Public Affairs; Stanford University. University Relations; Stanford University. News and Publications Service; Stanford University. Office of Public Affairs
- Faculty-Staff Newsletter, 1957-1968; 12 volume(s)
  - Faculty-Staff Newsletter, 1957-1962 (Volume 1)
  - Faculty-Staff Newsletter, 1962-1966; 1 volume(s) (Volume 2)
  - Faculty-Staff Newsletter, 1966-1968; 1 volume(s) (Volume 3)
- Campus Report, 1968-1995
  Scope and Contents
  Vol. 1, no. 1 (Sept. 18, 1968)-v. 27, no. 39 (Sept. 13, 1995).
  Issued by: University Relations Office, Sept. 1968-; Office of Public Affairs, 19 -; News and Publications Service, 19 -
  - Campus Report, 1968-1969
  - Campus Report, 1969-1970
  - Campus Report, 1970-1971
  - Campus Report, 1971
  - Campus Report, 1971-1972
  - Campus Report, 1972-1973
  - Campus Report, 1973-1974
  - Campus Report, 1974-1975
  - Campus Report, 1975-1976
  - Campus Report, 1976-1977
  - Campus Report, 1977-1978
  - Campus Report, 1978-1979
  - Campus Report, 1979-1980
  - Campus Report, 1980-1981
  - Campus Report, 1981-1982
  - Campus Report, 1982-1983
  - Campus Report, 1983-1984
  - Campus Report, 1984-1985
  - Campus Report, 1984-1985
  - Campus Report, 1985-1986
  - Campus Report, 1986-1987
  - Campus Report, 1987-1988
  - Campus Report, 1988-1988
  - Campus Report, 1988-1989
  - Campus Report, 1989-1990
  - Campus Report, 1990-1991
  - Campus Report, 1991-1991
  - Campus Report, 1991-1992
  - Campus Report, 1992-1992
  - Campus Report, 1992-1993
  - Campus Report, 1993-1993
  - Campus Report, 1993-1994
  - Campus Report, 1994-1994
  - Campus Report, 1994-1995
  - Campus Report, 1995-1995
- Stanford Report, 1995-2015
  Began with: Vol. 28, no. 1 (Sept. 27, 1995). Ceased publication in print with v. 41, no. 33 (June 17, 2009).
  From June 18-July 2009 replaced by the online service, Stanford University news. In August 2009, continued by the e-mail subscription publication: Stanford University eNews.
  - Stanford Report, 1995-1996
  - Stanford Report, 1996-1996
  - Stanford Report, 1996-1997
  - Stanford Report, 1997-1997
  - Stanford Report, 1997-1998
  - Stanford Report, 1998-1999
  - Stanford Report, 1999-1999
  - Stanford Report, 1999-2000
  - Stanford Report, 2000-2000
  - Stanford Report, 2000-2001
  - Stanford Report, 2001-2001
  - Stanford Report, 2001-2002
  - Stanford Report, 2002-2002
  - Stanford Report, 2002-2003
  - Stanford Report, 2003-2004
  - Stanford Report, 2004-2005
  - Stanford Report, 2005-2006
  - Stanford Report, 2006-2007
  - Stanford Report, 2007-2008
  - Stanford Report, 2008-2009
  - Stanford Report, 2009-2015